Oh!
That's great!
I'm going to get shampooed!
I'll do it!
I'll get the temperature.
I'll have the temperature adjusted.
I'm so embarrassed!
What is this?
My first shampoo in Korea!
Oh, I took a bath.
First time at a hair salon
Beauty Salon
Amazing!
It's so smooth!
My bangs are still a bit messed up.
Look at it like this, it's so cute!
Kiyomi
Hiyori, Kiyon.
She's got a little bit of blush.
It's a little more baby-like.
I'm so glad. It's so cute!
That was a surprise, too.
Next preview
Next preview.
I heard about all the foundations and stuff.
I asked them what they use.
Some of them even showed me pictures of everything.
From the stomach.
And then, you know...
I said, "Do you sell it?
Souvenirs.
Let's take a look at the base.
I've never seen it before.
There was a camera in the makeup room.
I think. I'm sorry.
I may not be able to show you much.
You always fight to your back.
The part where you don't open your eyes.
I can't really use this Jeria.
So, I'll just show you the cute part of the finished product.
Just here.
It's really cute.
The makeup is really beautiful.
So cute.
Okay, I'll put it on.
Hi.
Good morning.
Well, congratulations.
Up!
Yoo-hoo!
Butterflies, indeed.
What's that? What's that? It's stopping now.
Wait a minute.
Look. Look at the hair.
Cute.
Makeup.
Did you hear the rumors?
I heard she was cute and had her makeup done.
It's been a long time since I heard about it, though.
Makeup artists always do our makeup in Japan,
So you come to the venue like this and have your makeup done.
That's right.
It was like a beauty salon today.
Weight? What do you call it?
Salon.
Do it.
It feels like I'm washing my head.
The shampoo's getting cold.
The shampoo's cold.
It's the first time I've ever done it. I'm thinking it's the first time.
I knew Julia would change a little.
She's still standing still.
She's going to fly away.
So cute!
It's tachymix time today, Yemida!
I'm super happy to be here in Korea....
Super happy to be here in Korea!
Hiyorin chowa chowa chowa
Everyone alive and cute?
Seikousei kippayo
Tokimeki ga Squeal Party
A party that will make your heart pound!
If only once in a while a hot spring will come by
There's nothing to be afraid of
Come to this sound
Bang bang, bang, tokimoki, gather around
Jump, jump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, come together
Arsic mirror ball
I had fun riding it.
That's OK!
Whoo-hoo!
Good night, sweetie.
I'm cute, I'm cute, I'm cute, I'm cute, I'm cute, I'm cute.
I'm a pretty damsel, a damsel, a damsel strikes back.
I like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like.
Are you guys going to watch this? Why not?
The colored circles, the sound of jumping.
Why are you all looking at me?
Weak-looking, crunchy, fishy.
Something's wrong.
I don't know what to do. Have pity on me.
I was worried my mind would go blank.
Surprisingly, we all had a good time.
Let's do Korean too!
Hello!
Good day to you!
I hope you can see me again today.
Please ask the Koreans for more chokki!
This is the first time I've learned something like this.
It's hard.
I remember this.
I don't know what to do.
I'm cold.
It's cold.
Cold.
Cold
I saw smoke on the table
They ate a lot of veggies
These are fast cookies
They told us this is the one we bake on top
We'll do it, seriously
Ho ho ho ho
It looks different
Looks different
Pleased to meet you
Nice to meet you
Goodbye goodbye
Me yesterday
The city after the rain
The waves are shimmering
as if my heart is in the sun
Puddles make a sound
I play the rainbow piano
I don't know why
When I smile, it's as if the world is shining
It's like the world is shining
Turn the umbrella around
I can take it easy
Because if I don't
I can't walk
I'm sure somewhere someone's crying
And somewhere you'll get wet again
I hope it's not too cold
I'm sure somewhere someone's crying
Just a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
Because I want to share
Still in front of me
A landscape I don't know
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Come on, let's go anywhere
Goodbye goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain
The waves are colored
On the canvas of a broken heart
Paint a piece of the future
They lead the way
They'll lead me to the future
I can say it now
I can tell you now
And the reason for my tears
Whenever you're lost, just remember
Even when it's raining
I'll try to make you laugh
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye
Me yesterday
The town after the rain
The waves are shimmering
I'll get used to it and it'll be fine
I play the rainbow piano
make a puddle sound
goodbye goodbye
To me yesterday
The city after the rain
The waves are shimmering
As if my heart is in a sunny mood
Tears flow down my face
I'm gonna wear a rainbow dress
La la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
I'm gonna wear a rainbow dress
lalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalala
lala lala lala lala lala lala
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
R&G
K 1914
Strong static control contains